{
    "id": "81d22ba2515d4ee399c1164409297805",
    "title": "Simple Past Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ..................... a strange dream last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "had had"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8851325577114ac9833c39b0c8303de5"
        },
        {
            "question": "The people ....................... at the bull thief.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "yelled",
                "have yelled",
                "had yelled"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e92d81dc7c4b451d96413123c1a572d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The young man …………………. his own life to save the life of his friend.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was risking",
                "risked",
                "had risked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "491f173e544943648e7817ea1b908f28"
        },
        {
            "question": "I myself ..................... this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "see",
                "had seen",
                "saw"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7871bd0dbce440c4aaa9ac6c000b859e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………. gently to the child.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "spoke",
                "had spoken",
                "have spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f7a261a66dc9428790bfde3adec549b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children …………………. their best.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "tried",
                "were trying",
                "try"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "46b679a50d0543d6aa7d7edbd986cd2c"
        },
        {
            "question": "The two men ………………….. ready to leave on their pilgrimage.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2ed08e00de14120880f5ac7365406e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………… at the entrance hesitantly.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stand",
                "stood",
                "had stood"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e00ef963335c45cf8f2922d4f4726ea8"
        },
        {
            "question": "Their families ……………….. them to prepare for the journey.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were helping",
                "helped",
                "had helped"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "faf5136c65404a67ab6203891395d03d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Kabir ………………… the value of devotion and humility.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "teaching",
                "taught",
                "had caught"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3f93f0e69d104883909ae41812934408"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children …………………. and ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were singing, dancing",
                "sang, danced",
                "had sung, danced"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e2961bd37551411d82df4284b8ca229d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She .....................…… a letter to her grandmother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wrote",
                "had written",
                "have written"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5ce6f5e30f8f4527aa649499b5d7eb88"
        }
    ]
}